Oh! Hey, Rach.
I was just coming over here to...
Wait, I don't have to lie to you,
you don't live here anymore.
I'm eating their food.
You?
Ross is on a date with my sister.
They shut the drapes two hours ago.
I didn't know we could
date your sister.
We know you steal our food.
I'm good.
Drapes still closed?
Yeah. That perverted couple
two doors over should've shut theirs.
-Is that a swing?
-Oh, don't even ask.
I can't believe Ross
is with her sister.
When Chandler kissed my sister,
I was mad for 10 years.
-That was five years ago.
-You got five years left.
-Joey..
-Want to make it six?
The One Where Chandler Can't Cry
Oh, Ross, hey. Hi, how are you?
There you are.
Can I get a cup of coffee?
So how was your big date last night?
It was okay. It was fun.
It was fun?
Great.
So did you guys hit it off?
I guess so.
So did anything happen?
Rumor has it you guys shut the drapes.
No. No. Nothing happened.
I shut the drapes to show her
slides of my favorite fossils.
Oh, slides!
So really nothing happened.
Something could've happened.
She really dug my slides.
And she was definitely
giving me the vibe.
Was it the "Please don't show me
another picture of a trilobite" vibe?
I'm telling you,
she was in to me, okay?
Hey, you remembered trilobite.
Anyway...
If she wasn't into me,
why would she ask me out again?
-She asked you out again?
-Yeah.
Tomorrow night. Valentine's Day.
The most romantic day of the year.
Who knows what could happen.
I might not be shutting my drapes
to show her my slides.
Okay! I got it, I got it.
I can't go with the "you
and my sister" thing.
It's just too weird, all right?
I imagine the two of you together.
It just freaks me out.
I can't do it!
It's okay.
It's too weird for you.
I won't see her again.
Thank you.
After tomorrow night.
No! I can't do it.
It's gonna freak me out!
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay. I'll tell her tonight
I can't see her anymore.
Ross, thanks.
Want me to call her now?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
No. Come on, I mean, that's crazy.
So, what's going on with you?
Well...
I may teach another class
this semester.
Do it now. Call her now.
-This is my favorite part.
-Me too.
I don't know what you guys
are so sad about. It all works out.
E.T. stays with Elliott, and they get to
be best friends forever.
You've seen this movie before,
E.T. goes back home.
What?
Oh, no, I forgot.
You know what's sadder
than this? Bambi.
I cried for three days
with that movie. No, two.
The third day my mom killed herself,
so I was partly crying for that.
Well, that I can see crying
over, but Bambi is a cartoon.
You didn't cry
when Bambi's mother died?
Yes, it was very sad when the guy
stopped drawing the deer.
If this movie's making you guys cry
so much, let's just change the channel.
There.
Joey, you're crying
over a Doritos commercial.
I was up for that part.
It's okay to cry. You don't
have to be macho all the time.
I'm not macho.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I just never really cried.
I'm not a crying kind of guy.
Come on, there's gotta be something
that gets you choked up. Like...
What if you saw a three-legged puppy?
I'd be sad, sure.
But I wouldn't cry.
What if the puppy said,
"Help me, Chandler.
All the other puppies pick on me."
Cry? I just found a talking puppy.
I'm rich!
I've got it. I have got it.
Pictures from your childhood.
This'll get you going good.
Oh, what's going on there?
Parents' Day. First grade.
That's me with the janitor, Martin.
-Where are your parents?
-They didn't want to come.
-Chandler!
-Poor thing.
That story doesn't make you cry?
No. Look, I don't cry.
It's not a big deal, okay?
No! It's not okay!
It's not okay at all!
You're dead inside!
-Excuse me?
-Yeah?
-Are you Phoebe Buffay?
-Yeah.
Can I get your autograph?
I'm your biggest fan.
My biggest fan?
I've always wanted to meet you.
Sure. Yeah.
Wow. Wow, thanks a lot.
I just want to say,
I think you're really talented.
You're just saying that
because you're my biggest fan.
Take good care of that guy.
He's a fan.
Bye.
So you saw me
on Days of Our Lives, huh?
You want me to do a little
Dr. Drake Ramoray for you?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
But I just got Phoebe Buffay's
autograph.
Oh. You're Phoebe's fan.
Oh, yeah. I've seen all her movies.
-Movies?
-That was Phoebe Buffay, the porn star.
I don't think so.
No, it was. She was in
Sex Toy Story Two...
Lawrence of a Labia.
And I got her autograph.
The guys at the comic book store
won't believe this.
Gunther?
Don't let that guy in here anymore.
He said Phoebe's a porn star.
Well, I wouldn't call her a star,
but she's really good.
You should check out
Inspect Her Gadget.
-Hey.
Ross just totally blew me off,
and he didn't even tell me why.
Oh, well.
The best thing to do to get over a guy
is to start dating someone else.
Oh! There is this great guy you
will just love at work, named Bob.
He's a real up-and-comer
in Human Resources.
Maybe I talk too much, or maybe I
should have been more aggressive sexually.
No, no, no.
No, that would never
have worked on Ross.
But you know who that might work on?
Bob in Human Resources.
Thanks, but I'm not gonna date
some random guy from your work.
Not random. Bob.
It's probably because I'm not
mature enough or smart enough...
Maybe he doesn't
like the way I dress.
No, that can't be it.
It's gotta be the smart thing.
I'm so stupid. I'm just this, like,
incredibly pretty, stupid girl.
No, honey.
Okay.
Okay. You want to know why Ross
canceled the date?
Because I asked him to.
You asked him to?
-Why?
-Because you are my sister...
and Ross and I have
this huge history.
-You want to go out with Ross?
-No.
You don't want him,
but you don't want me to have him?
You know, Bob in Human Resources...
I can't believe you did this!
You had me doubting how smart I was!
You had me doubting my fashion sense!
It's not that big a deal. Just
don't date Ross. There's other..
You have no right
to tell me what to do.
I'm not telling you what to do.
I am telling you what not to do!
Why are you so jealous of me?
This is not about me being jealous.
It's about you being a brat,
wanting what you can't have.
Can't have?
Excuse me. The only thing
I can't have is dairy!
Well, you just blew your chances
at dating Bob!
-Who?
-With Human Resources!
Jealous of her? Who does she think
she is, Princess Caroline?
-You're jealous of Princess Caroline?
-Do I have my own castle?
Hey.
-Phoebe's not here, is she?
-No.
Did you get a movie?
Yeah. Yeah.
But I don't think it's the kind
you're gonna like.
Not more movies that'll have us
reaching for the tissues all night?
Sort of.
What's going on?
Phoebe's a porn star!
-What?
-Yeah!
What are you talking about?
"Phoebe Buffay in
Buffay The Vampire Layer."
That's Phoebe.
Where did you get that?
At the adult video place on Bleecker.
And I saw Joey was about to go in,
so I ran in ahead of him...
to surprise him.
Then I pretended that I didn't
know he was in there.
Wow. I mean,
I just can't believe this.
I mean, you think you know someone.
Even Phoebe, who's always been
somewhat of a question mark.
This is so bizarre.
I guess it makes sense.
She had such a terrible childhood.
I had a bad childhood
and I don't do porn.
Yes, but you're dead inside.
I'd better take that back.
What, why? Why?
We can't watch it.
It's Phoebe.
We shouldn't watch this.
Absolutely not. That goes back.
-Maybe a bit.
-The first half?
This is wrong, you guys!
Phoebe's our friend!
-I'm not gonna watch it.
-Yeah!
Good for you, Joe.
I thought I'd find you here,
Nosferatool.
Are you going to plunge
your stake into my dark places?
Actually, I was kind of hoping it
would be the other way around.
What's that on her ankle?
Her ankle is what you're watching?
Well, it's hard to tell.
God, if she would just stop moving.
She's just doing her job.
You sick bastards!
It's a tattoo.
That's weird. Phoebe doesn't..
Wait, that's Ursula!
That's not Phoebe! That is Ursula!
Wait, wait! I can watch that!
Rewind it! Rewind it!
Hey.
What's up? Oh, my God!
What am I doing?!
Hey, sweetie.
"Chicken Soup for the Soul"?
There's no back to this couch.
You hate this kind of stuff.
I figured I'd give it a shot.
One of the stories may make me cry,
then you won't think I'm dead inside.
Oh, that's so sweet.
I don't care if you can't cry.
I love you.
Oh, that makes me feel so warm
in my hollow tin chest.
Stop it.
Seriously. We get married, I'm up
at the altar and I'm like this:
I won't care.
I know that you'll be feeling it
all in here.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
And if we have a baby one day...
and the doctor hands it to you
in the delivery room...
and you don't cry, so what?
If we take him to college
and come home...
and we see his empty room
for the first time...
and you got nothing?
It won't matter to me.
Okay.
I won't worry
about this anymore then.
And then, you know, if I die...
from a long illness...
and you're writing my eulogy...
and you open the desk drawer
and find a note from me that says:
"I will always be with you"...
and you still can't shed
one tiny tear?
I know you'll be
crying a river inside.
-I love you.
-What is wrong with you?!
-What?
You can't shed a tear
for your dead wife?
I left you a note from the beyond!
-So you didn't mean any of that?
-No, you robot!
You damn kids! You ring my bell
one more time and I swear..
Oh, Jill!
That's a game I play
with the kids down the hall.
They've really taken a liking to me.
What's the matter?
Rachel and I had a big fight.
Can I come in?
I know we're not supposed
to see each other anymore.
I don't know anybody in this city
and I need somebody to talk to.
Sure. What happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
Okay.
-You know what might cheer me up?
-What?
Seeing some more of your
super cool slides.
-Wow, really?
-Totally. I loved them.
You could finish telling me about
the different kinds of sand.
I'd love to. Wait right here, I'll go
get the projector and my notes.
Thanks. You're such a good friend.
Have you guys seen Jill?
I can't find her.
-No.
-Is Ross home?
Maybe I'll call him and see
if he's seen her..
Who is it?
It's Phoebe...
"Phoebe"!
-Hey!
-Oh, God!
So you're making porn movies.
No, I'm not.
We're still rolling!
You're making one right now!
Let's go, Phoebe.
And you're using my name.
Can I help you with something?
Phoebe, come on!
Look, I'm talking right now.
You mean her. Oh.
You know, twin stuff is always
a real big seller.
What?
I could talk them into giving you...
thirty dollars.
No! No way! No!
And stop using my name!
And shame on you!
And shame on all of you!
You're disgusting!
Especially you, with that!
The slides are almost ready.
Yeah.
I know what this is missing:
Alcohol.
There's wine in the kitchen.
Oh, great.
What is my sister doing there,
and why are the drapes shut?
Okay. Rach, calm down, okay?
She's really upset.
We're just talking.
She's making something happen
with you to get back at me.
That's the only reason
she could be here, huh?
It couldn't be that maybe
I'm a good listener...
and I put on a great slide show?
Ross, I am telling you,
she is using you to get back at me.
I think I can take care of myself.
I'll talk to you later. Goodbye.
That was your sister, actually.
She thinks you're just using me.
So?
-Hey.
I just came from the company
Ursula works for.
Oh, no, not you too?
I went to get Phoebe Buffay's checks.
There were a lot of them.
Nice!
And I won't have to
go back there anymore...
because I gave them
my "correct address."
Isn't it gonna bother you
that people think you're a porn star?
Oh, no, I know how to handle it.
-Good.
-Yeah.
Trying to figure out how you know me?
I'll give you a hint. From porn!
Yeah, your pervert boyfriend
watched me in a porno movie!
-See?
-Yeah.
Hey.
You may have been right about Jill.
I knew it! What happened?
She kissed me.
What? You kissed?
Maybe we should
give them some privacy...
Look, I tried not to kiss her, okay?
Doesn't sound like it.
It's easy not to kiss someone.
You just don't. Look at us
right now, not kissing!
Let me finish, okay?
She started kissing me...
and I didn't stop it.
I guess I just wasn't thinking.
Yeah. Let me give you
something to think about.
Hold on! But then I started
thinking and I stopped the kissing.
Thank you for taking your tongue out
of my sister's mouth to tell me that.
I realized if anything happened
with me and Jill...
then nothing could ever
happen with us.
-What?
-No, I mean...
I don't know if anything
is ever going to happen with us...
again, ever.
But I don't want to know
that it never could.
So I stopped it...
and she got mad
and broke my projector.
Wow.
I don't even know what to say.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
My God, are you crying?
I just don't see why those two
can't work things out!
All right, I'm leaving.
I'm not spending one more day with
someone who's out to sabotage me.
That's you, Rachel.
Yeah, I got that.
And you! I throw myself at you...
and you say no? How gay are you?
You take care, Jill.
Okay, I'm leaving. Don't worry
about me, I'll make it on my own.
Who knows how I'll get by,
or even if I'll survive.
You can stop that now,
I know you made up with Daddy.
-You do? How?
-Oh, just a wild guess...
and your limo just pulled up.
-Sorry I didn't get to know you guys better.
-Absolute shame.
-Okay, see you.
-Bye-bye.
I can't believe Jill's gone.
I can't help it, I opened a gate!